Now, we should be able to find the most
appropriate URL that our app should use.
现在，我们应该能够找到我们APP应该使用的最适合的URL。
Based on the UX wireframes
we saw earlier, we want
基于我们前面看到的交互图，我们想
the weather forecast for a week's worth
of data given a certain postal cost.
一个星期的天气预报，给定一个邮政编码。
For the purposes of this quiz and our
example code that we'll be showing you.
因为这个测验，我们的例子代码将显示给你。
We'll be using the Mountain View
postal code, which is 94043.
我们将使用 Mountain View 的邮政编码：94043.
By all means you should use the postal
code for your own location.
你当然应该使用你自己地区的邮政编码。
Or you can use city name or
latitude, longitude coordinates.
或者你能使用城市名或经度纬度。
If it doesn't find your
location based on postal code.
如果基于邮政编码不能找到你的地点。
Try using postal code followed by
a comma, followed by the country code.
试着在邮政编码后面加一个逗号，再跟上城市。
See the discussion forum for
more examples.
请看在讨论区中的更多的例子。
Next, we want the response from
the server to be in JSON format.
接下去，我们想要从服务器中返回JSON格式的响应。
And we also want the temperatures
to be reported in metric units.
并且我我们也想要以公制单位输出温度。
We choose metric for
doing the query, but our UI will be
我们选择单位做查询，但是我们的界面将
able to displace celsius or
fahrenheit based ion user preferences.
能够使用摄氏度或华氏度基于用户的配置。
Wnd we'll just do
the conversion ourselves.
我们将自己做出换算。
Enter the URL in the box that
fulfills these requirements.
根据要求在输入框中填写URL。